Address:

Bethel, AK, 99559

Phone:

(907) 545-2329

E-mail:

anastasia.caywood@gmail.com

ANASTASIIA CAYWOOD

QA MANUAL ENGINEER

https://github.com/Anastasia-Caywood-QA/Anastasia QA

Experience in test planning and analysis (mind mapping), experience in test design techniques (equivalence partitioning, boundary values analysis, pairwise testing, error guessing etc.), experience in writing checklists, test cases (Google Sheets and Excel), and bug reports (Yandex.Tracker, Jira).



Experience with:

- DevTools Charles Figma Proxyman Android Studio Postman
- JavaScript JSON/XML Apidoc/Swagger SQL Terminal miro/Xmind
 GitHub.



EDUCATION

QA Engineering | Yandex Practicum - Moscow Russia 05/2022- 10/2022

Bachelor of Public Relations And Advertising

The State University of Management - Moscow Russia 09/2011 - 05/2015

Master of Chinese Studies

The State Academic University For The Humanities -Moscow Russia 09/2016 - 05/2018



WORK HISTORY

Manual testing specialist | Yandex.Practicum, Moscow, Russia 09/2022 - 11/2022

As part of my graduation project, I had the opportunity to test a web service for renting scooters, including a mobile application and API testing.

- Working experience in requirements analysis, test design, functional and non-functional testing, creating Mindmap, writing bug reports
- UI Testing
- API (Postman)

- SQL
- Proxyman/Charles
- - Git and GitHub

Client Manager | PAIVE Media Group, Moscow, Russia 02/**2012 - 05/2015**

- Managed a staff of client service representatives
- Enlisted support from the marketing team to reach new clients
- Promoted cross-departmental communication
- Collaborated with internal teams
- Communicated with management regarding development within areas of assigned responsibilities



SKILLS

- Jira
- Software development lifecycle
- SQL
- Test plan creation
- Regression testing
- Application testing

- Manual test case preparation
- Defect monitoring
- Documentation skills
- Communication skills



Content covered in the course

QA Fundamentals (free course)	10 h	Pass
Test Analysis and Design	45 h	Pass
Web Application Testing	45 h	Pass
Mobile App Testing and API	45 h	Pass
Database Fundamentals	45 h	Pass
Automation Testing Fundamentals	30 h	Pass
Graduation Project	30 h	Pass
	Test Analysis and Design Web Application Testing Mobile App Testing and API Database Fundamentals Automation Testing Fundamentals	Test Analysis and Design 45 h Web Application Testing 45 h Mobile App Testing and API 45 h Database Fundamentals 45 h Automation Testing Fundamentals 30 h



Lyudmila Romash,
Representative by Power of Attorney
Tour

Sergey Brazhnik,
Director of Mandex Edifect

1.11.2022